[{"topicId":"15","id":"15000","langCode":"vi","question":"i+gvOjmq9Tva07NcXTj1D/39Cm3cUSZfqSAL+pIq9PBf/W3kwMOuwkuolXeEKpQFgwFEhOvfa9GlLv7NlMhw5iNi1xkA7sJXXPGR/XncboQ\u003d","answers":["what","when","which","why"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE4QPt5q0AsWDmPoPSoVEP02F5lnZPIYKk4xky/BjHqtFSRknZ5U8QHp7Gi7zmfCM/SqQIen1AM/JvnYF8X+wA17M1RO5qjbzvra5pcGvzwGFoyShmsb6/atYJ2bgWaWGYclGbHsz8/arAYerwWpS/15wfMWnOOH9ywDaeeaUwKxQNugABFnsNYsibHUIQeau+yWjKN2F7lcSif4aO0o7NpzOk2upsPoRB4e4Jw5SbaE6RQ/WrNnumBh63WdSpvP5q7ZvoI+P4i0lpruh0y1qiWC4XG3HytfO04kmAvOQyQ2q1J/NTiNSWNeFsvHOTGHMftzYZOtHXyOLQMfx0K343COSzys1yR2c5u9O6mqPlwmS7r0YMOJ8ZvW6pzq//6E59wPoHcphCYTWDJG969LWF7VMbLbbEMveo6PQ9mmt1bZ59HoGMdJfdTcCvo9gHdfeaBY7awG2BBFhsQmIbHVbm52Fodxkmc9kYJTve2nVID549JmjnVbEuN4C/vh7tdcD3g\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15001","langCode":"vi","question":"SzxhW7OhPLDaN/lHbVBCKKY7O2tq3UPGHoAaacboE0Le59lL2Y3j9JhLT7rCjJbLds+XX1XzG2lLsOTperAI8lsOvHILXiAaNpjwmy0Q9Ub+6m+A7svcrCld1KaD4x0ukExO0HCobOEinqRb1C42DbVVDg3Yo9ro6rngSmU6Xxk\u003d","answers":["when","who","what","where"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE4QPt5q0AsWDmPoPSoVEP01dUlThWjU+Rg2f375jaqA7XPdpbyORH61zNwrgAZuelmUh919X0GOPcZiCsQxCIj6RgT4GimqXydsp5aqWYKl/Wm/LoBqQLrrEKthtNxx0ilRUHKAU60ekuOuEogVVjVUiS/FQBznIltiamzZG2WGmTSRQkngoOVFEy7jwvJMd/kUnxSwTUO8M0TmXTLp6OGTug9VfQbDSlReG62l2lM59zdL01QoFlDQMi1ehtYU7JwS1Za6waF5f+XVgLLxv5rKlzfGImzM7F9L+dUAYbB1AvRaZOIJGbNUBR4UIHsWbkvwjLnhBmRX4YB929K105wgCU7JFeeYaAjGshRxVkn4MYz0WnE6CteFVy50w+3lBjXkVln0ceaqhi7qLo3OID9WPuopabTvkRjvTARw3u0xT7r0YMOJ8ZvW6pzq//6E59wPoHcphCYTWDJG969LWF7Xp20peuNHV0tpjHPS5GbnB9HoGMdJfdTcCvo9gHdfeaB5psDvHFC16tGirpqR/UpHsf15ek66ClpzMUV+VOHGpV09IqrZRlDOXfw+eFbzpbL0QppCAVkSuj7Kl1yUc3uuBmG+fb5Q+e+GCAgTy6uN9X/DMK0e5h6ab+qqOVQ4h4roCCj9XLdbQeloyr9lg+2A\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15002","langCode":"vi","question":"YsqiALW5A/6EQfeGfObvoPNLwPIdxAdrRckVMAxjZ2EePyvOz9u2esbRhEF6eHDS25m3h89PL5vwS4leA6nBwrlwH8xRyG7Lky3dy/4bNPs\u003d","answers":["what","who","which","why"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE4QPt5q0AsWDmPoPSoVEP01/lbUvbjHx6Iqc96t+kv8Fg3kgB48PtDHqpJ8tMR2/S7WVsNycOKlwFn1gbONgdd1eok7JxWpRxgPr0GZcQ7VniOOQUEMvjyYSIiad9r/8jECrlf5QgWLk3BpIMu7fvYADaPdoGoYFhNy7J+wIW0yWcrx4FyVShrjjTnHdEtP5qF6pz+gGB2L/ze9kueu3yFBPQIfKnnB3noHtOg61xLDgbtSUlSHVCl0d/OgwJBAgqDnmVH3neXtFzx9Sfi5e8QWfstv04JbKIucItNUgTQpMs/Tjc/JljACk9W3ZClFB6X3M0pWLeTWq+6yHJHJ87HHV1UEU3b4ryUOzvSpgB6wCjSwTczAmJsUbI7EjRZ5XhBbt8rGv9+nHHSKdMg780x9h+6N85IZcwpcNBsrM97zr7r0YMOJ8ZvW6pzq//6E5945PioE7SqC5bVtWpul3lB0kNXCOuzKihoFtA3zsaXFvl70V5fbjm/WEHN3NnveNo/R6BjHSX3U3Ar6PYB3X3mgVCbJZljLvx4Wn6Nx38AdfdyR3bdvmuiCOQIIeW0XKUaWzbqrLEnMO++fBczir8/a/uXU7UUoKykzRmtUa5MCxuXq1NObZ5zk+v1AkWhQln6sYbyNPiBRJW2jyGtqyojA\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15003","langCode":"vi","question":"P1MveXYtpjfImhTXdljJwjlUvKl5DlfaOKAsal6qv9aWF9u6SHX3K0QKoA7WA+alEiEzSY9DtMWzwZDMSkw1bw\u003d\u003d","answers":["whose","when","how","where"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE9Zgb55rSwyQ6mnEOMFGHeCfOa3CeglkzVXz/WiOz5gi9HoGMdJfdTcCvo9gHdfeaDJDMCaYHuol8AyHuCEI2f7WjxTjY6XTLioaEzIFL7sZwF6vri1yR6cMC1lJY0C7tXWEUsaloI4zC7RfOwuEk/EE63sXXT6jNxY4oQduW9H2cLkZ69K1X45Ta0WAGJiQrR37s5ZntVCgKg9DsNKbyw2iPzdV4VWQJW7sCNNVVDB8onrc5RbbnprkDayEne234IPPiVGPhRfYtD1/J2iaQTK9EKaQgFZEro+ypdclHN7rPDaFGbfe2vgEVGOgVnmj2dsqwxgdBmnTB+w/Z1+tclP0egYx0l91NwK+j2Ad195oHmmwO8cULXq0aKumpH9Skf6YuAiFBdrXFzmwtLnkGHhYMysFgnyaGUUjTVsWLiIHjVPynuxtDRxt0nQtlG00biWQzTTUtyxlqMJRO03FLyKu8tU7r75NG/5deJHR9enmp4YIqgh3ItgPDe8Hcf2pOsEyTx92BEhvJAeSM9jJjk1zYHGoP+0SbiqmZmyraHp6"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15004","langCode":"vi","question":"7550c9BmMI0Fv+lXzQvADOYs+pyF5/At4QSaw3bD9LfE6nOGE0Ejl9dL3lYe8AOHAEnqFbtShfUPZHQO7rVozA\u003d\u003d","answers":["why","which","when","whose"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE9Zgb55rSwyQ6mnEOMFGHeD/G9nOjf9e9ZpvsIFE1K5gCak/px8cmgrtXTUJWhAPtMH2D8M172bW3xgqfKkIk38m8AOEF2Pk0Uw761ZeoFeQ7k/EkKW/sMLvI7ZirwY4eo2P8XwpjmhuKiIukRTByuZQ5BR/yvs5SV7B/Gs3aM6tx5yTzik3s4QPkVWWrEASajmgdV3BY1a0QGdcbV90NO+u51uGBhq383uBloY+jYNyAfOdmL5HeHUMdk70OLvX7IXsVz0XyzqM5TDmVbpj/DJHUXKQlsg3QQ7fawaxXRPN5qZg1nqLCDAOK1cLyaIVEhrQs+FQSHl6cv3iFWUb0VB+zFIcU/gXG521X3lvQs9nUWx2XaYPuInvHrTMAFRbv+69GDDifGb1uqc6v/+hOffXEK9KKV62dOK1B0pxTu01jZGyu6EnOtBynb+yemlkWdEj8X9xQWtNwyyGkOLoFiHtCFy8WOkpoj3j7knqVXGFNUaH1bJP0KUNBt6NM7J+QJ3xzTwEwFjT/CN5EBA0FYBPTxxD/OTqTqVBV4MItY1knLmE9G5Py8rX/hdGrPYITQ\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15005","langCode":"vi","question":"HAdNZX9UegOrX1Z4VD+9xLlJPhR5RdpkeT06ivmWXiVUjhoU114o4OXEE2UXlUZh","answers":["when","how","why","which"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE9Zgb55rSwyQ6mnEOMFGHeBUmL74qYqB884RSuM/UagFYyJLWyuHBWz3NX75Jm5SmTPtajT5fiLuQ3pG1mzpXqdC2rW2q4GCu47zcL7JLx74GEf0GNv5+VrsZf3nws2EftlYlsfczgpqyCBdd2Ywy0uDTBdwNNAmQvgB7FDjpKy3DLVAxe4hFqvmuYCUQ+5nS7LdV2u7m/kdUDhlj7j+Pg0DGFY0+4RJYU1Ff7rRDuhRXfqXSdlFXHd/5HZpsljdy+G4x3MzlMacbG5kxARW1pybJLmJy9WFg5sqBk6ODddqeTr49Nhgj+giPmLVDT1u1QGegDwQ8wSgGdMUG+f3pvOcoyJxK0llvm0G3B8GruK8vz48dBDJWzro+kClwlou7/YzVjX63Hsvxunx3wyRDkNLSqliknVhIiCDwzEHfb2267OG5rbJIwBVrOK8jpTuNANNH+eZFvuJ+UK7IkPVNW9/9PQPtonOdmpwGdTg5qhVnOK+ClW4ssyO2896G2wtyrgidrOIBdvCILTjvO7DVdVnDL4L3+NwusIxfj01rc7iklOUn0yuDbYvQp1P7RFsrRbPqPE5EpesNUssFSCh+G29JcOtmxKU3EkI5sYIkkk2eRVlo+4RkfrfoicW3AzdVuluzxGtmaDjBi7nrlMPLbXUn81OI1JY14Wy8c5MYcx+3Nhk60dfI4tAx/HQrfjcIyaMadmxtH+luj3tP0x9QiAJqT+nHxyaCu1dNQlaEA+0v84QGkGkqU5yd/+/og2FBEne0/AVfakOT94MaD5eGJOh3XvskwlISdrGz6yPYtkppbNuqssScw7758FzOKvz9mBBy6spvEI7c1FhuSspyHPQYHBO7+jCoc2aMqTuU6ueJFEsb/PxIE0JySt1QElavG4aFAaH8gfRs9Y/TbyYn8H3tXq6Wp9cy+2lSSOhy9dh"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15006","langCode":"vi","question":"P1MveXYtpjfImhTXdljJwmf77bWEOEsj/7ktqADGVEPAHfVLgFVHHL8HEWuM2bZkoYdpuVFOHq5dxEEyPNm8EVsMAuj/ttpDDBz6M4/XoVg\u003d","answers":["how","where","whose","when"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE+SxEbEg5DchXqXFOXrU4soFe3GX/Q6Bypo7X/PcPeVohHk1T+Vj715YPfNy+nhawes6U/ARWQ9Vhc+7TC9jpOLXpAONmj+bqrrkFr+SwSQNFFSa5m004+9dY3cl/MWGw9g2Om8lGxdiuacuzySSF2+0G+lVov+NNUkaLdFPJJ1J4BmUjIDLk0wUMz8gPduKu+WaNGQJRW9YqEAU9vYe9RsbSOC/szXAym0dIk76oCVQMvJRLSi+AtuidiFU8rPuRYZuK1r2IQNpRGYTGaKePQ06F/lOs6xHUPchP2+WVkNHA3P+lJZ2PWnHvCajRR+FIq+ZnFHGXgWGac6UYgUgMzzYejmIjVkamvdPb67mI/yzjA79B7fSvLoI8RGG1mrriaWzbqrLEnMO++fBczir8/ZZbPsnD0nSUqOykCPJqbGP0CEflW7Lmay/SBvvscoPSMrt6key4AdabjIEI7Uz/5brBmqPn9fOlbl5FwxDViFa01am96lgsqqcJHFjoTZdZw1PoL3pdcvXNzuKg+Alt6VbfqaEFpDzo1dUFM6+59ssF2byElbprCwBaayrjYm4B7VVDg3Yo9ro6rngSmU6Xxk\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15007","langCode":"vi","question":"yIJPJGA2z7ei0CKL5+wUTXMzKyrYKiykyYP/Uclg2wnxlpRZB7W1BXhl0ygBuFcD","answers":["who","wherever","which","what"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE7jNKtqifOOtqoeG9Sdv8yZH4xVcQShK8S9KrkgqPsP3DlzHCnyI0Y/6m5PJGsvM/tfnpbhe8mm4rOI5FzabGyLT2I1PDzqeNr4GUtpzN+EIaEi23ViJEyLKn9jjHSnmYNOqUPmaMT2sYlIBWuinkpOpAND1F625kFH9STgXZFpQQIQnZDHCmjOSIplAlQGjzqc9HZkcdOgoHNY0AxgBI1bSrUevi5AH4beBuKXViL8+Q4RgtYoiDDyKmbozIHX3epN1zMDBTYiHbXfc/HX/xBlIy7NSASRXG1G5VdTK/9MG0EBm7gex2TMOx6vN9sLoJNxLpcJEOnGkslwcW5jhP9KvmZxRxl4FhmnOlGIFIDM8lTpOVAjhZhoYib8hQQR0gpnJGtLajEF0ktpzRLLEzixFHyHycG9JvC8LOn2hNnTxNkk3Rbna5KFrE0O79PCJ9uvr4WU0PsWkyxev2FAXoL7meVlVbXs9LuMeSDbxmzqBuYjyeGWitPWL5ZxrjQvnE6WzbqrLEnMO++fBczir8/a/uXU7UUoKykzRmtUa5MCxuXq1NObZ5zk+v1AkWhQln6sYbyNPiBRJW2jyGtqyojA\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15008","langCode":"vi","question":"RwSfMXx+rGZsQ8H9ah/Z+NKeZK8lvuAolTs1DU5AcAcL+q2hYi8YVBkkc4MNvaN3ZFtln/2AKYDowGa0UGrmeA\u003d\u003d","answers":["where","why","when","which"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE+SxEbEg5DchXqXFOXrU4sqcOwn4GxnJXg7T02g9lQU1Llw+a1AfHtSPNO1FrM4OOYLN1rE6Z6tXCmxSOJvS3hfeScpzFo5OLM72f5GhgxY7aVhQGNJU+QtDxrdfUz0iC8yt8AP+UJJX+1NBdPkhVyVMQgKnk3ywaPipfo0ekNYWjnBnouuOCiINabIOehDMBhCoVI4MWGgl+NwFR9/tvQEZZfoowCXvo7orSAPr1HON6OOOAqfdEaHTuhwDSzMZ22ccMpbQrGdE33crHIw21RBQ5NE1dGjiIp4tq4j+CQ4nTwADLe9IkGlkur1tXj93egYpKqYd9geQAXXGncobumelcJWC3Rei728NKujDESJNfoK1SIWjtbPyeC2inR6mqvR6BjHSX3U3Ar6PYB3X3mgVCbJZljLvx4Wn6Nx38AdfRV4YmSnFHbrGDtaV2z1UsvhvlvObxDVnNwG0KwoFnBSSAOsw709fuNGFHY+9E3yxqpx0mCQhlxw+nGkWn/a5we69GDDifGb1uqc6v/+hOfezw2E+99jxpdyXT7U8ipTzms3PPSQPIY80e4vktGi7i+HwaUxxWIbIm/chFimMsD4\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15009","langCode":"vi","question":"Vfbf2K2ixv6/35KFAgwkPUTHcYEqSpzqkN3crfIICn5y9zfBwdiYcoK94tarBhnJ4nd/GheeDyVqyyWfLJcfVs2B3dtyqIGup9K6ZcQcHDJrqIi1ZgoyUnZHKat+CXozhG8yGSMvH/7wUDZiLf6R4Q\u003d\u003d","answers":["which","whose","where","when"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE+SxEbEg5DchXqXFOXrU4sr0UYglRAUwfbohMpsfXYgcrkqYngTnqi9s3luHi8yjc96/3IgqhJmnLFWazLoh58cdmURYo012OMxasutsZ4Da3ZWPh4SJjnImozu51ZELIhnM5+jx7Uvv8lXeXlbwUCTtfmdlH+tDxeMLgwWyJt4pEKhUjgxYaCX43AVH3+29ARll+ijAJe+juitIA+vUc41tmT2RO+VlotXhCHYjbT2WZhT1mJP3GGwPzjm42f/oS/UPloZWFFNQPZXw9XH3dFX++HVPKsvTaxyreIZmrYa9u9Xi86mrncyumBsYZs2WloERjHBgbx5i9H3+cGn6C1ncDVZ2xTFnWosHRM+7YV6dXz46ZAqBrxwYfeh28HiGiHzo98XHJcNVJXqP+c8mJUjNNUWwwaYf3PCpLJDWpLsf+G+W85vENWc3AbQrCgWcFLwcTUekzeCX4pTegNXqAXKBdComkXeLatDXoyb68cI80U797YMav4Do7JiSO0Gt6qbfpOlcRG80Q3rAU0AAGX/l4lrqGxCzc58s4oeOPUWh7r0YMOJ8ZvW6pzq//6E597PDYT732PGl3JdPtTyKlPOazc89JA8hjzR7i+S0aLuL4fBpTHFYhsib9yEWKYywPg\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15010","langCode":"vi","question":"jPwcD8W74YQFHsaYgF/EjARbitK7VzsdvXQ+ZnUdKEZOStAktQ/6KqKMQPZjrDzWHIsJPHZMfrosKtjujJceBg\u003d\u003d","answers":["which","why","whose","where"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE1fi7I6+dAb3eyrkcljZmf0HBXhl0cLeNjK5UXifKQbeI1Z16Eem7LP/Krn4EnvbAILcGvmfsaxBoDgRSRyh9ZQomjlombTkeOEOjpir/hcC2dKxULO7/5yLkIvyBbUAyL+HhlWbrqE87QXj+YX6783AXq+uLXJHpwwLWUljQLu1dYRSxqWgjjMLtF87C4ST8U/oWrb+0GN2Wc9xreFfToGiiY41NVumhE+xvi1dcND47JfxthZ/dAAQ+VqrSPaqIGFqLONztirItWcI67N2V5CCDyQso28zI0lielV2hiuB9Up374QnTUoV85ID7jm0+qWzbqrLEnMO++fBczir8/a/uXU7UUoKykzRmtUa5MCxuXq1NObZ5zk+v1AkWhQln2e445kDO3YzGpMz8ei0mGv4b5bzm8Q1ZzcBtCsKBZwUGc02qI4n2oAL1FnOt1zff3PdFepuoqrMhjpZrKkrp5CvtS6C2IJ1ALkh3bWKyEln6wZqj5/XzpW5eRcMQ1YhWv37hR45/3RDRGEFv6DaLuIhuvmh22+niCWRrqpdP/Ul"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15011","langCode":"vi","question":"RwSfMXx+rGZsQ8H9ah/Z+PXTJ+olHd4OfPwnW+VJi6uDBLb5ecKQLhMaghYK5aQBs/QYiPdKMv00DezH3W67i+nRgpP71YzotcRXCt5jUd+i93hw/O56jmbFNmMx0xxf","answers":["when","why","where","whose"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE1fi7I6+dAb3eyrkcljZmf0QdqqWaZ6J/AmvFO62ehJLWV48+hLmpzo2UsINqiDW0lP93vCfaMEHSVoagd7Nh/qQ7etdB/AFF9G8do4FIWlKJFurUQWTji23dUNQYr3p3gLsgLAzYOm662fRfiAWivcqKqn1KK9y8rRiG9hI91XClOWJDFbzlw9MTJPPqlX9a/LjZ2y64pmsmfeStTRuF1ld18uTke3XzV5N4lc1nxRA2J0EE3jUN8JbrZ4+QtUr63W/MvdQKOwmFWkgTERwhoVCa03c+QALYjeJhhIMiUWUKgsE707REO7gcEVqG2c0xjT7yaikBBLpmQkaXr+PWLddFSlw4Y7NTw69jRHXzHeNoLtmud2TVDzQZOUqEewdUItWOIK7Ltaxw5+ThBqmRgH0egYx0l91NwK+j2Ad195oHmmwO8cULXq0aKumpH9Skex/Xl6TroKWnMxRX5U4cakJkhFYBI90L8HOaHdFT/Nu5LubTjkfXF2RC5z0/BxG/zTzowfYuHxQ8qV1NldT+lVLwMZm8NKLBGYiIvy25hb0rvLVO6++TRv+XXiR0fXp5qeGCKoIdyLYDw3vB3H9qToT1bcJV0QJ5f0INpBxKnJZ"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15012","langCode":"vi","question":"9FU48k89o9khlBq+o2oLLT9PsO2HJ+L+msH3HG7TnpYbVv9owMlyWXUfchMQVFTOhLa6JuqEUiF/GuMqSSpk2Zej22udadc+0mxx/aRl02jt2Yp224DfVhSpZKmoLPuJWVFedeke0n13r9ytGZtqArVVDg3Yo9ro6rngSmU6Xxk\u003d","answers":["why not","what","how","why"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeExY0LE1ylIqCxvfNHw53VodIDpi2vfz68g7wTCoDYFUBHdgNe/HqCjsZ/tVuWzCGs/Vh/QlcXEo9lsvumXknRFJ4sFs/3ElrnYunKSG+no024G55mlL70bNB5quP8nvlzaLxvcxhQLMQrXT30+QAtLWpboR5AutHq1bTgc1BztWexs8REl6AVcSGraTcMYPYEYpppzKXEFtheMQF1XXLxiPSV3SJ1nI90DjbnvNki69Zc1IQH2fXVzp2KntbVkWr7LgidrOIBdvCILTjvO7DVdVnDL4L3+NwusIxfj01rc7iuLfUFMJhsj9O4rZQsENzwF20xp45ij6GXhOZ2Hb0shJgeR0b13nd2Jn+oOTfpuqa7EYBq+dnAUv+AJGQon99ycwuqET6V4QYMDea60YLTWbXw7BzFnoS0vaLyOtPZxf3lhivOEDAnlL8WrEVxdPriFLPNPhb8NtsgX/oWMoMPeCS6bniRiZMSejqHLs/Q8S96Sga2A34/8tpSTCNcAIj8O2HeZuYO7JmGhusQZTCaVTzmTuZm7JOWP5LAi9f9dklGtCz4VBIeXpy/eIVZRvRULDlxpRYl2I4X1tcZfG+Qd/0egYx0l91NwK+j2Ad195oHmmwO8cULXq0aKumpH9Skf6YuAiFBdrXFzmwtLnkGHhYMysFgnyaGUUjTVsWLiIHjVPynuxtDRxt0nQtlG00bocsep/fLq1YCmACH63pSIpJGSdnlTxAensaLvOZ8Iz9w+h+gByvFLPWvXDWajAzo3oXviuql84doiwkxzTk62D2TIFPN7r9RgA9v1Jz0JbX"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15013","langCode":"vi","question":"aU5GxETFrFWSUW86R9PWxpva8TX3z1DEr2ZX0Ju4n5sdBdNx2Surgj86iKcKqHcDsCgGB8g5dEHdNgvPpBCdYt6RX9ZAzS3dzgiUESk2QuY\u003d","answers":["who","what","why","when"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE1fi7I6+dAb3eyrkcljZmf1YJnuymilUNPSN17fDo6vuCgiMXUdk7zzPCaAXNhmJP/WoNnGneGe5CqcrkWTizqrjexBDWeEZWwBCgJptW2fq21aFFMiFeAl4JcjWZYcb9FDkFH/K+zlJXsH8azdozq3HnJPOKTezhA+RVZasQBJqUaISa6V4UaEXlONnMPsZKkMV9573ohrzNfGM2QsuafPGkgpF1zJZEhGBuTtpKTeXLBPH9bOlHjgvPgf+X5yYnq7XlJ3pV7n8xJ35xQ0J8qJ5i7PRikmTglAOuyh33yG2GwUyCgqYVCHP5deFgORn6iJEO8Hl2HFHb/Qm+A1SVUBJGSdnlTxAensaLvOZ8Iz9w+h+gByvFLPWvXDWajAzo3oXviuql84doiwkxzTk62BsGaotkJgdE2WR514e0VgJrvLVO6++TRv+XXiR0fXp5qeGCKoIdyLYDw3vB3H9qTr3EBSJuYwguJPKMNNaG7N0THAdHu0fMlLnzE7VYe8aYhrQs+FQSHl6cv3iFWUb0VCqNKwzz8esQl+CHbOSRyTT7RT001XPVZ8Y1m18NkKr84RvMhkjLx/+8FA2Yi3+keE\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15014","langCode":"vi","question":"nMI2ufdf/HJ1LN+Ldwz5iXkrYEb8y5iBLhZTJnH1wbK/SaweHLSyXMJlH3lvD/IpuUI2iijlOlF+YZLGw0XXlg\u003d\u003d","answers":["why","wherever","when","whoever"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE/EUrcLtpTsvAyCA1FlXD39IDpi2vfz68g7wTCoDYFUBYx1U57uvn6NYP6ew5zl7SE4Si4Q/AO5QdGQBEFGNYRFmTtdVENJhChdYlnkdimBgPZcQnyyMLNrf7UbY3sEb0jQgG5yNHVO0DdhOkROkQ1i0W56hq3feINkxtupAQjHcQKuV/lCBYuTcGkgy7t+9gEg0A/iQPdTCHAHSXJ4T0dFXpEN4YxFSJNyvC8qMRrP07r0YMOJ8ZvW6pzq//6E5945PioE7SqC5bVtWpul3lB0kNXCOuzKihoFtA3zsaXFvUpeXFZI54mNoQOaI/ogSF9KesMF/VS6HaZ0/Mgpp9QRt5VJfzEDQNu7Lok0CCNWP2DY6byUbF2K5py7PJJIXb9BfXrIZBCJUj3uYcvMa3BJZOJULKaP7Z8MFw4yHEbxMQeG8Jb6Re2/zmQ5u7ZNB2qtuCDAHPMpwfzxSJ6lCHz7rYiLaJLi/xWQa76KR4LwIwJDPD5ei4vEvsHlvQMCgVYR5NU/lY+9eWD3zcvp4WsFdwa1qD2LOtC0AZ9MAKLs0pfmuXoaPx13MaZGp8aY2ltSfzU4jUljXhbLxzkxhzH7c2GTrR18ji0DH8dCt+NwjfCa+7Ja1msHau+v5pxZ7+NSfzU4jUljXhbLxzkxhzH5s1age0AujTkTm8NLafnyUcrc/V31Y0yReWbq142csNs0njn1iJMhoK6DWWQ34a2iL8pJwQ2YRYZUYmcl/8HNywtZTQhzJingOTXmg3ibpvXrhjsBlrX/ukvgQau/cFalQcV+tpOD+i5Uk+yGg4xgKtVUODdij2ujqueBKZTpfGQ\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15015","langCode":"vi","question":"YsqiALW5A/6EQfeGfObvoFSOYOcXl1oT3p+F6KABZ5+x2TwZjUBBtz5zY02I4q5Q","answers":["why","who","where","when"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE/Ebqxqv4jwG+/3SifMXzOWjZw0adNG9yQb7gxrGdHWoBFu1sqln5xyYY8ERrIEfBEPp7FBRpA14hYzHT3oR39MoLlET+BMJ0/dNe2JkAgAFNokBYS+/LG4aFB5DSqZmJpqjbr8nS1iRoG/D0umS/TK+ESik/pftNmoELtD2ZAPSUuTh20bfTJfrY/uwCeDRTf3JvSGq3XJ3y8nhhycAsN8Rbiy23WpQqr2eP+14cam41J/NTiNSWNeFsvHOTGHMfmzVqB7QC6NORObw0tp+fJQTwUWcnDm7a5dlpGDkHgWprXVfo6khSFn/p5MZGrnBNakgGZafZx2d7+KT33BDVHgvRu4UzaaN9Y4Yj2cashIxUOQUf8r7OUlewfxrN2jOrceck84pN7OED5FVlqxAEmpGlXl0JRemyWWb6iqbUNZfc7wCbnLmuBcRmMFZoagmZNuHMZcoZLq+6xbGcNhR1hwMBs8NXz2CPsoYirgqyw6kh2hkTwV/I8Aw1NQhhcy+GgNz/pSWdj1px7wmo0UfhSKvmZxRxl4FhmnOlGIFIDM82Ho5iI1ZGpr3T2+u5iP8s07XWlrOG6HcnFfe265cZPfku5tOOR9cXZELnPT8HEb/dZ+x2lLOigxZCKffknEf0ZP6SWfuf0cht/JdrC9jFB6C3Br5n7GsQaA4EUkcofWUof3+LFhIqFbZX/4hB2QhGq49EOQRTW1fozH7iWG9JWY\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15016","langCode":"vi","question":"06LD5H1DgSeKHZpK487FyaFGNoLTiCBHuvnBqQmKdQRnbs1ynYqTiJwWvMXG09XEXGH9NQz7RqKcxKUF/sNMVsEy2mXpFdqCw4F2PW6sWJM\u003d","answers":["who","whose","why","where"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE/Ebqxqv4jwG+/3SifMXzOX3qhkmVWXDPD6y6l9k5Uo1pbNuqssScw7758FzOKvz9oCWjP3FbcqNkV6oVh9oq6wTuXw65k8NOM/HyL4vEBZa/nSdSwLOb8o9JWgD+CL9cvLjZ2y64pmsmfeStTRuF1ld18uTke3XzV5N4lc1nxRA+odqhv8qtBZB4nJQ/St3Xo3q18+NISt06QBWwha/rMhVdLjNA7szWcV2gqtbZ+U9lTKF/af8+2BhCFTk4sMMWEeG9ircu8U2tDYB6j4TAXtCRTnN9ldxrK6tgcia//x+ChSVgo+pF71e3/pgRZcIdaWzbqrLEnMO++fBczir8/YTHOTmSFCK4LvN/xuU4M6aSpJlEJYq1/qkp/mEXmSKEg52okYWOW2lzAQtlQnvSgOC3Br5n7GsQaA4EUkcofWUJd6Gg86UfXZ76x0RyRhY0iWgtsEz83QTcJpAV2vAr1b0egYx0l91NwK+j2Ad195oFQmyWZYy78eFp+jcd/AHX3HsH3Po2cvsRJANEGxnZNw\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15017","langCode":"vi","question":"U45NyMTY+96bCuwCBkMIGmjQ5qWY0fgPY3vz0Ol4qpNicFaMU/tVXzH5UKRZ9ip03ZGBUL5jmtg6ipCC24boY96DmhitIlcj+W4SL/h2V08\u003d","answers":["how many","how often","how much","how long"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE/cWfVVpYrEWxRlkPbTNcqTYUu2EjyPs9s3iDmEFpA84zvXP1WrD549zmicb2sjqkB+LPqY6YLOPeMt1w2HmIEVtPSmjMOK8WOjsEiChY3pAC/Zf/t2H/psnBAE3kdYDnH55Ng+yXq+4huM1aw6ChZe84CPA55bx8gookriRqUN9yUZsezPz9qsBh6vBalL/XnB8xac44f3LANp55pTArFBULyDr/lMIpLlrOBuqKqGixYLSpYgmG8p7q4ZrKaI0obPVgU+nfCyB9yLXkzzL6YWvRWekWdT2pr7MJKEQljG1Ssv0tk55r2h09miPm304Zq4kCrZnNi02IXscUCWWlNfpgNq0UchqxYmovvlyV1Bz7sPg6xVSVG6LSK9ujnFlx5YiEmauU6QBaUJNOQNCKx8j41Up56sacM+u5hcveLKcSROC5u2ioVWuCCITHe6lNAYab5eQxrTcZJXUeE7tez+XYgbrwOqdl4WmGsdqrn7YTj4rxJJE4t5B9gYk7Gf4rxnFnYEmMTGQht9vciuGDLHycv64WiWEA1/O0gzN/Te3vR8LiXZ6Dkvhsr3eaHrcxI96CXU4z7oWBqfM1ISE6nL4+yRItCHrkj+oIb+GiPOjh4mQsRpMkhBNEJar3rv6XlMF1WNAxdXCwXY+2fqZ2d2empE6EHLqJuj/JO//+f7FP7T/E2A+td1agn4VTnbGI6W6MkdWGRpjWm+Vv0lJPQqRiqnUFVeoSYMz8PHysDCTI+sRAG02IWp4F2jneLIghNHeAwgbVcE56yOhADUDasFBaGlHLbZ2EXujaHPFCI1KQlyv6oDK6jFaHQyLAAVg+QSdGtmtDTlstLE8It9XxptOlythu+vkOTe5jyXR/lniBc1bjf5zNdJIDNmwhjADZtRSYfxWCq2UnJNHHfabEE9x+VD08hmXdsAQdHuEUTpkHUpyjlwhzV9nfRfuxcAtJW7IB9fO+UwRvWd1xzkoECIOxQjSvQUq1hYBgR9H0PjYZcTQ6EAiU4b5ag72zHwdCj+EGX1kCLkTYYhh2mATFwR7z8yMwx/IiQG/LybuHGjkjOGcFeweUemTCdJpwmmTTNX6RA2r3Dj7v/EXz6ApHezppiyywnCoSNG8glUbT2I7iCJxorZG3dA9PdvFsnxHzQ\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15018","langCode":"vi","question":"aRVkOZADsdLC+IASCWSwSo9odSHXG9CBc7LmPOTWE34mlCqtsw0HV4g+zXPCmQinUMgngxOy4Mt1F+RMnx6r0ULTa7ap6fkT8nSUrL+N3t4\u003d","answers":["how many","how often","how much","how long"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE2VQ2jb1EsDMutY5vXXBwa1nwLlvsF9xKYnTXEpT3R7PZwAWOQJibC6qqktB+QHXNhcmGWOLmUym3e90cX65ICiCEDCxPVE+PzUgWoEMrczZf4aHd3EJvx9JCoIQqEn2WK4M5fqIh7qEP0k1xonNe32NeRD56Dy/IQVrUiuypHxdCmbixED9L2gWx13ECCQzR8DBW7WHKCOp80PLZ2bksuRQ5BR/yvs5SV7B/Gs3aM6tx5yTzik3s4QPkVWWrEASajrqwBfToWtbEQzOHX8Bw4YJ5XMMIUSwa9//x2GhR8ESADEGB86lBVe1JlVY5AKvDpoX19vRSYH1qc9CfC3Rr0ShBN015ZO2Z49TDha5jXFeg80wKFr8MATfVB2xAaWKQrbZvK0mnlxai47Oy9TpodkX1i5BJ+x2e89YWBNwGYK7CodrBh1yg84ehG+s6t4DjpXjcBbnq6PF0kUiv+NYl9OU9CQ5wacULMjuxGBZeRkHlODIHHYN9RHVFp1hv8pFsdqy6s6bX3JJjfOPFYawOaVRZKAU2cK563Yv11hZJegfyzMIcJrjsQRr5676OnAwS7DU23YdPlNUGi4kN1lhAroxkrm/Clm2cpBZGncmGCDnD4WJDve5KJeeCiWgeGX7IXa38RZ2sWwu6TP1PBAoMziIC8HCw1d1mOAsAeDghRrwR3JBRdppuCllNeWbbJ5637O22b/3O6REhgLtunZkG/20zsKBbIR+3mF7PAh6yo17+beX/fx0pqm4HweId5N7r1UANKdL1T/1gD3sf2szXDJu9wT3FhKIlZLOPKLlA3zWGp2SYWhnDYfqltElzMbRTE5kTJmTCqB7u38wqKkozx1MXDoc+Cloyyi1IoJuS+YzHZkSdBdkXvRQrXugaMedAvyqg5NZ6A8q1S3wa2ew0yT17/zbor9D3aa5Jwg6f07GNYLLLn+ptDtKHj+O8B1NMonLbZxENCjx2bx6S5XVWfz0LRcfEmKFMuxjFkaSry9N1J/NTiNSWNeFsvHOTGHMfkT0+PsJWGa2DkNpETcC3TMPhYkO97kol54KJaB4ZfshnuFfOl19FFZzhX51wR3naJPnN/bFg9jX6NcU4BTM9wdN91/GRHkBsSS3XlpN9VfijABySEh6Oj79Inc3F4Q9xw\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15019","langCode":"vi","question":"+yiglndRdI7+bzoZEJe0Ia3kca/8rUiLOtQOuVzi4fTM/Dpy91kwXsM5xn0uzbp4JIue0WmmiamRK5SGsLbjy3akK3axCe2nelvnojWLs1A\u003d","answers":["how far","how many","how long","how much"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEwftIF5uws6qeBdRP/PKAa8aPCCMQp8XAnN69zU8ET67GrapIJ/nNzBM9N6s3srYNVuX1SEOMN+VUw6Fi3W+xRwR+c8Wwa+Cy74rlaFJCvARCAppsxEBhodyAEQoooWDkY3iBUx9/s7DpL3HIgd0vQxxamOalQLLZtFfPvSWrlqrmfrIdts+YCDw34kH9XbyX+tXFhe6461K+upGKUqiBgWRW/uyHM72wD0xJzkeIIoDlFBDYoC0czfw6MbYUAmbRCmoPtZ+gJiGz5G5GmdTwC1on3iATJe0A1yNGWl+W2euL8jx7RfkHBFZiQcSiibaqmc74b23xGM8wDQ92lx96oam9JuRxuaz7K0P719a0Nj0eCwXLTCX+Efj6q7NFNQUBlNbfFFEOEI4ioAybiPtkTq4aig45nnJiY6QPBsI19FFAImgoZPFYXNrG2q+cO/6AlbKsyas9P219GrJPO5+PegjPaiZEWju7hCq6hf00dVI+sJ/EF6GFFK3HZFUFCHHKXKnCGMxAZGhOV5EHxg6RIdWFkIqNp/WFCyIG1Lb/ATBWGYC52BQyNR3/lRbWqaKZWk7E4D16ghwzU6SrTk+ssB8oP29Yg3BrJFWcvDkYeSZdiRK+xsZnUx6C36fIatdEROk9gKCidT3f9mQQZvwAL1YfkqDeGmNe3cM31E9QUU7m/ZzyzruI0y1msLdg0H3brqT53jX1dAncqP0T/aneDwL+UvN2TiVtiW85VnsvKFA4FwfX7Q//795r7Y/7XRsGM4JR5Smt3SJJqlncm1c19byLo8Db+yH9XP1kDUCqiHEQQeH1EetV9skj1ws1ci1cd9zb5ZU3l+Csz9UNebgy9WpzvZSnH1hGqNZnZzITszFWD0S/Ete7c9/US+QxXqGBPmmySwwes/Z+OjD2pnYhc9NViovQTCMb6Ax7IQoohaZ3x0KOeq4U3EPGeSi11j2ydHYp8s5iDoYSbURGsEDpYE\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15020","langCode":"vi","question":"Q6Lh5oVMXuNZBZ+tlLIDW5onGW1XNIyfMiWzhcPPs5pQJ8NJPzPnEK0YelEH1SGL+zjmxfCiXsAHe2xIJ3+St+wWnhCI97kNvFw5rgBsdPc\u003d","answers":["where","whose","how","who"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEysvqM+vt6AqRDBodwagl36PcG7pDpaJEow+jsw6j0qzr5mcUcZeBYZpzpRiBSAzPCO72SlP8XCfDaQPztpPxLffZGMDyfebt/qE+4MzTLKXOfZuruIC3PS3YET+qLZIWcRWd2CSXI2xdpMqHVLN+cIA7ETc2DigNTiaJ+xKc50YVyxQaEiF7+1ao6M0H9PWLrj14wQLJ7wLN+9sPmrfqnLIxHI5LL5Iqd1kzQ+zOocnCI2gFg6NIMHTls/VuaY6ot8XzKt66MZLTsIAXQoAB1CMvWgsk8Ywtgz+0Mc/0FJk4k3traSHiNjDid+ffEN6aylyv/kXZXPAVE5IeBQIhi9vdgUd6daGfU8Cry6ic99M50p/yipamAvVPRjdrzmLYRR39X/KGuxbA7Lcl7q8CjKdZVgTJURYWo2OsGz+9nIpj3flxsM3IviMMCpW4CvXhoy1n4JyzVqH65QHg3ISrgUafSGNHSkOiu9BvwwyN3CmDhGO2/XC4aVWkwh+NEAV7Vb0HYrifhzaoVu4sy9DlwX/th4/pvCeyQGrRp7pwpqlUs0pei4ctSs3dw0xApIaqKBKniYjUj8ls47SfuNeGmnr3fdF2FAZCC4tTAgMNHvZkKDZOIFn6JP3ly35B+5cMt6/3IgqhJmnLFWazLoh58c9Uu96U4glUt3W7vp/2TLVpW//afYqMtGboX4j1V+goDy9PE7V+h+/640yXd43v9lkDAx3G+Ptt+d4Jf7RJjopmSH/z2P4lINqEcaDnHXfEr0QppCAVkSuj7Kl1yUc3uvTC70Bhl0PqRi8owCbuQX6WpRFgNnOz/3T5JCeWzCb1w\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15021","langCode":"vi","question":"QPP+NIZLI1EqAbQtec7bGtV7twtM4Ec6qUzHL/wnKUKfhWL9xC1SRT2Fec6yHP0yhG8yGSMvH/7wUDZiLf6R4Q\u003d\u003d","answers":["whose","who","how","where"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEysvqM+vt6AqRDBodwagl36PcG7pDpaJEow+jsw6j0qzr5mcUcZeBYZpzpRiBSAzPCO72SlP8XCfDaQPztpPxLffZGMDyfebt/qE+4MzTLKXOfZuruIC3PS3YET+qLZIWcRWd2CSXI2xdpMqHVLN+cIA7ETc2DigNTiaJ+xKc50YVyxQaEiF7+1ao6M0H9PWLrj14wQLJ7wLN+9sPmrfqnLIxHI5LL5Iqd1kzQ+zOocnCI2gFg6NIMHTls/VuaY6ot8XzKt66MZLTsIAXQoAB1CMvWgsk8Ywtgz+0Mc/0FJk4k3traSHiNjDid+ffEN6aylyv/kXZXPAVE5IeBQIhi9vdgUd6daGfU8Cry6ic99M50p/yipamAvVPRjdrzmLYdc3mOZ40uqGAJ+hiTjw/JwAFwhI/ipC1QVjRMQGcBk0PsWUKMzCHXLq4RH4Mz2iV4rguf54S67N4pw2EhsgS8ayFd0omYbIPpqQYer6iPumTw+h46QIDkyfk67Oaz6uhfR6BjHSX3U3Ar6PYB3X3mgeabA7xxQterRoq6akf1KR7H9eXpOugpaczFFflThxqVdPSKq2UZQzl38PnhW86Wy9EKaQgFZEro+ypdclHN7rgZhvn2+UPnvhggIE8urjfW4tQWWlgZqYankETdqA5QHUdoxgfFyTKlBFF/Rg1UyXEJYuap8sdaDOZYcknpbVLeamYNZ6iwgwDitXC8miFRIa0LPhUEh5enL94hVlG9FQfsxSHFP4FxudtV95b0LPZ+XV8UiG1efnwPlK3T3FmL8\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15022","langCode":"vi","question":"0e+ZezJqCXixzilJhXd6Bz69rIrTMFmFCNSyyaeAf/yszy9y41UtSPQUwZOKzM9qd3pqc5+HzL7LPEBhafjecQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["how about","how often","how many","how long"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE7pbJEpRbguzhKwRAsivmlpMq3Yu4/TG6uJHxswbAyPWL9h00rygBqx5qi7ly1QzZtCKMusICyyh35aDJ1HS4D3M+LeleJpDLFHjuiPcRbwsom9cEOl3k+90MryeyTHxqfJdNWuzVMFi8yGeYCF0lKxQ1oCIHnSWM81XBNty8U6xWM78nRLbVoHcbqRsLWDTpwcR8zeLcvxnkSvsFHhlrBG4BXN22hYRpqt959g4thMr6vVdzcJgLegDxUuIlTwQ/llPE5FQAAc9dHYc/2HQu4kFinJ/8cQBCJDrc4P6bKROeCaE6qhb6rsZFvugKAMJnFIV7U2Iof7vuFpXwkbzbpN1V72PEX/StwTr13kCahmvgUTfx/jCpFuuqSbzqUHRpYmRilKwhkLWj8sN+gjh6t+wCxGNHphoZG4DY1ovH+RgFyYZY4uZTKbd73RxfrkgKIIQMLE9UT4/NSBagQytzNl/hod3cQm/H0kKghCoSfZYOR6+ZOBy9z+g1g3PmRrs6UCBB8n3PhYrVlYjDeh/lPMSc30kMnry4H+g9JKOlBiCFZXW4+sSgATbdxF18n8ko6ylaTnQbc3/zmRDH2+s8dmh39Snn0K5UdshOt2I8HdIBm7yU1LkP54Dl84yF6+lp9mj3D9qdSEAK715AW2sMzVQ9yhCTmkvgEdLhHPz8zViGPRSR2rNhm5PwfJ5OJ3ABWMZN7HojYN3pwCg5Z5tzTyf8c+BxDbr00WAlFSEswlbMEnARmxxfLEtOl1R5bIE6QNqUdMBl+9greKsRudeqfOEbvObFRVCT3mSwl27ph4jHuT5S3XkjreyC7MSdDtWD3L/RMvwOhxfLJEn9adWdJ9BaNo8/58qqt8Zj4iLl9AfngrJ1Afzq50/7GDu/uu7J+78Y7DpPZwBq8oa2S/671OhNATY4y+xkqsvlh7w5tDGEc3sLlfjePmYf0pHbiMgrITQ4Hqwv6+rqXWBfWB1Qe5jSQU5GC8d1EIhzTdeUv7Go55GMi6PTN7QPiVloD6V+w\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15023","langCode":"vi","question":"VdG+lcRrGYYIU+RhQqajZwPxroptgDYVcUM53AkPGMizUSRVrBZ0z4S4oq7DPhuBlUlWmWB5RHI89o4rCiAh5g\u003d\u003d","answers":["how long","how often","how much","how many"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEzlQWKZDv9ThlkKJV8NbPSnMWpFxp580EA1bjXYKCRN0tbktaj4Z8GKJvVHv8YXiVhcmGWOLmUym3e90cX65ICiCEDCxPVE+PzUgWoEMrczZf4aHd3EJvx9JCoIQqEn2WDkevmTgcvc/oNYNz5ka7OlAgQfJ9z4WK1ZWIw3of5TzEnN9JDJ68uB/oPSSjpQYgqlx5Pb9vEmI+rsJIhDoOqovgCyUWczvK1vxsDByUlf7HxrI+8Xm5ZVeA3fUfYZiFS+5wgN0ihHGmKmU8zni4Obp9Wwuu0bbJMSsVhwu39zseMcdeBSGKFDrx0C9yHZjYsBer64tckenDAtZSWNAu7V1hFLGpaCOMwu0XzsLhJPxLzv/aox+2JD+hD/Uc6jK8JIHBEgLoUiMdz17uhzhu8DSooqOCKXUv48cHkY7eQzMAuIn4K0iFzPEEJCekvdE/BuxAlI4bIPD/dMqX/mTp3rt2G3mS6zvG/nnR1a/Y1VOF9YuQSfsdnvPWFgTcBmCuwqHawYdcoPOHoRvrOreA46V43AW56ujxdJFIr/jWJfTnqSv3ddER5sDBzlaFqUBq6F1uMOO746Q6jiFad8fdTkOsbiDvGh3K24gNTGXsR7oUN+GEQh2sqgKP0T6ZQdqWIbKSHpADRIKKTijsArsK91K54CKxCqZG4IxEKMgvM75W3n1Tb2naD6MeOyUCVMvwOgd30YCTJ0dTTM9r7WXcsPFNO5OFSEhaWM1FphVQuuyMrmXy0TTnRHIOv68HlJmgKylaTnQbc3/zmRDH2+s8dmh39Snn0K5UdshOt2I8HdIBm7yU1LkP54Dl84yF6+lp9mj3D9qdSEAK715AW2sMzVQ9yhCTmkvgEdLhHPz8zViGPRSR2rNhm5PwfJ5OJ3ABWMZN7HojYN3pwCg5Z5tzTyf8c+BxDbr00WAlFSEswlbMEnARmxxfLEtOl1R5bIE6QNqUdMBl+9greKsRudeqfOEbvObFRVCT3mSwl27ph4jHuT5S3XkjreyC7MSdDtWD3L/RMvwOhxfLJEn9adWdJ9BaNo8/58qqt8Zj4iLl9AfngrJ1Afzq50/7GDu/uu7J+78Y7DpPZwBq8oa2S/671OhNATY4y+xkqsvlh7w5tDGEc3sLlfjePmYf0pHbiMgrITQ4Hqwv6+rqXWBfWB1Qe5jSQU5GC8d1EIhzTdeUv7Go55GMi6PTN7QPiVloD6V+w\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15024","langCode":"vi","question":"1KU5S7vix/3iK5Ay28FdC4e+Z4QR6i1ev6Yw1q/1G7fS2M3xRW5kufOGjnwV5bifw9+Y7uD62PS1IedpBpL1vORmBf2Fh5EtfGWSTUnG3tB3empzn4fMvss8QGFp+N5x","answers":["why","when","which","whose"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE/QH+Pdy7OgSVBbX8nh4IEFhFzPfYVkjLDWj9M4vjBS5UAJY4+li2SRZQkS5xIsOHXjjC9EU3ci9Jn+1q/t86MOS2N5xogNtQXanxlQcg8ZHzk6XYiHXOw943GyBP6Zl/5yMA1lF67KmrKV4/LaADB47nHX6a+0GQPWyv1JkIq/smCFE8oTB3MIV9Jo/NseWC/qKbyGuenAj7St36YQYybXb6tbZ9H2pb6HGplfjSg7HM9hi7dqYaUiMqB2zvUUDDG92BR3p1oZ9TwKvLqJz30wmFPnA7s5LW6Bk96msBinKafDVqZvfcUKjTJdToH9siHSaotcvbW6h5hDPRJiaoiUD3OHguLr+iJ14PBaCCjCePN97/nkYuw+PTM1OhNHEvz6my2tz0tj3qr4/C0Ufe0N+GsGOS2BBtOhsoi+lPRlpF0Q/HOiyV6KUVRaHBmbfkQmpP6cfHJoK7V01CVoQD7TB9g/DNe9m1t8YKnypCJN/qOFe2UyGWnQcPoyGmB+Jz9SfzU4jUljXhbLxzkxhzH5s1age0AujTkTm8NLafnyUDLghvAD4k3lLYIQEC8rC+yuahIQ1q6Q0H0Z+QIOfiWXev9yIKoSZpyxVmsy6IefHetbWh9CJ0m96RR1y5IQNGA\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15025","langCode":"vi","question":"IloorXmIHO72GOS3c1RzUW9F3nl8+TcEX8efr1kdhXoF78QocdnGme8fHnJTUIS0jExgeeG/TYIw/KVbdYJw9g\u003d\u003d","answers":["when","why","who","which"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE/QH+Pdy7OgSVBbX8nh4IEH1omFPLC7k6jG9rYVyB6jJhHk1T+Vj715YPfNy+nhawUSbICZhKzUxVIm452MFoIEBidMU2pajxP4AQPMKl6b0GmWgLgC7TLVkPxULBe/5bVDkFH/K+zlJXsH8azdozq3HnJPOKTezhA+RVZasQBJq1o1A+hvoMfj2fMpa5GQFZ9S9X4LROY58pY5B21i8u3z18AtBU6ZydwLnK737LGYuGDMlOGfQ8C390gK7rUScUP2aTNoUO1euM4RzBHZ2a7TrBmqPn9fOlbl5FwxDViFaYlto4MjWzz3DQXaEB9DaLtSfzU4jUljXhbLxzkxhzH4hHKnlX9thRtNGz23j2LdGoQ2OyZDSwAxacfS9ZdToYVLNKXouHLUrN3cNMQKSGqigSp4mI1I/JbOO0n7jXhppWjS3Iw00/y8cixK3z7Gt0DSeAFI+jBtYiLHC0bdo+xc9hzLjUZfzVxcgFPVaLccTuEy071zQ2HcViLImV3t/Hg\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15026","langCode":"vi","question":"zP3Hz8UXndLYhknPGmkBm1s6SNcPhHHM3T6P2RNkNiFmRpiassr6lYTTJAk8aar2HY5HYjcSzBr/3LWl/Lwv7XWw05//V77BTPL9g1k8ifodUvLvz2iINKvprVUu6/dBe0O2m2WWIFer1Z0HlHHPHQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["which","whose","when","how"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE/QH+Pdy7OgSVBbX8nh4IEH1omFPLC7k6jG9rYVyB6jJhHk1T+Vj715YPfNy+nhawUSbICZhKzUxVIm452MFoIEBidMU2pajxP4AQPMKl6b0bNFXHl55lDn9R2EYtS+to/LjZ2y64pmsmfeStTRuF1ld18uTke3XzV5N4lc1nxRAi+8WEuG8ExWMUpyD7PYr9xuppRQkzCR8nJt/Lh3D42GIthI3I/FVWo1TfDe5vqVOsRcDBBLonmtmzB0gtPEE2WgVeM9E3y0In1arK0TZlsocShJUanw915XiwHasGW1I3Oo4uWoIY8Hj8Gxr3H3qErebKGfo+Rshprmv2oJpz8wnwVe7rDgsokTz2VwiSw2xpbNuqssScw7758FzOKvz9nK9nSk/GA1btqLYMP1h3oVsAipOoFRuAO8vBeth0VOjhHk1T+Vj715YPfNy+nhawes6U/ARWQ9Vhc+7TC9jpOKekY+Usr5mmX2UGsx7aGWS9VI8it/aTPPpxAtO8cl0peS7m045H1xdkQuc9PwcRv/0tt4VHM5DscIY4kxjsei06GEy3AFkfYRIXep3wQlvgaUWwuG2wS9bwUr7sQKWnhDp9BBIUEjxVJ2oTimAK6CUlUYCYTNHCMswBDopvU+LqQ\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15027","langCode":"vi","question":"/2Pgm0g9tGBdraPuL57BLHu2xjkQNMK3PFWdyeW5gzqeZhk1buGhOHK0kN5p9BXxrERg/wJKZ1jVrvFRFlD5qA\u003d\u003d","answers":["what","who","whose","when"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE1NeDDp2Z4LIAgsQAkGKixHsPg9lcanoLWZziOZfX6bK+G+W85vENWc3AbQrCgWcFLwcTUekzeCX4pTegNXqAXLaH3rNJ1HuLV/oKgrri8LPh/hv42ByxzWSLbHRi5Er6R/awcaTQeWsihKCqqJle8U6MVHzCJ9oQRlrqG2xKXK1+TymtOtnucv3cCtiQ6UwEFLNKXouHLUrN3cNMQKSGqh16MSUn+fMVqRHbFBxOdEtEpX7wPWqoC7KIFJfqZpBElcYVb8Jp6apxWU03+tzkQLIWfLGAv71KFyEmiYCw+uTEq6dBr3nxe+qY4KaBgRlXVbz43LesgP6QHaeq0Z4BphMLbobA/+05iKGNXbNzfukUs0pei4ctSs3dw0xApIaqKBKniYjUj8ls47SfuNeGmmhr+VUoYal5F6ESiZeTaWRrvLVO6++TRv+XXiR0fXp5qeGCKoIdyLYDw3vB3H9qTpUdFyK6KJUSrWLWG2iL/pURQuUqfT/koB2HebaS/iRN1b72CDvRx/zBjMKjPqjXRRHu6LAtJkewFYU2JHkqi15"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15028","langCode":"vi","question":"+V9EKLZvc+aINjBQlzQ8g2dowrde2jhVFsYpk+OCVwJ+DrumjmS+ylrFCanhPJQXMsb/qziZst9w5Ii2yKmFcA\u003d\u003d","answers":["how","whose","why","which"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE1NeDDp2Z4LIAgsQAkGKixHJVaxbeESfDZ766VhEda9krkqYngTnqi9s3luHi8yjc96/3IgqhJmnLFWazLoh58f6mQtKTut92C2y3MPh7SQdL1sSrBQHnNJtGKTbERJZM07zJ0oDlEzBZLEbJOBGEbs0ZkIoKX0CN0BVanFVMSfuuCJ2s4gF28IgtOO87sNV1WcMvgvf43C6wjF+PTWtzuJAW72po4bCA1MBWR1OkvDexfWM0REbPElklGMTvVeYCZBe8zsT1N/+1LpSRZOfJHvWc1Xgi2DhBkyvsuMoG14NdDOn/x+ckxv2zGUfbw7kFCkCXwjPg6KE9LYFoLw/MivuvRgw4nxm9bqnOr//oTn31xCvSiletnTitQdKcU7tNY2RsruhJzrQcp2/snppZFnRI/F/cUFrTcMshpDi6BYh7QhcvFjpKaI94+5J6lVxhTVGh9WyT9ClDQbejTOyfkAZQ55VC+XqjsOh+OtTJJ1Fr5mcUcZeBYZpzpRiBSAzPCO72SlP8XCfDaQPztpPxLffZGMDyfebt/qE+4MzTLKXOfZuruIC3PS3YET+qLZIWcRWd2CSXI2xdpMqHVLN+cJdXxlqgJ+5iOsm4pcMlaMZ"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15029","langCode":"vi","question":"j8kS7gc0nh1SNp4G+6CEkdbrGtrQuT4+lT37IwcKHBTjZktRtmfulpXC+aV7ZoNyQbp9GVC05Ra7vPsa1+fqYg\u003d\u003d","answers":["which","what","why","when"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE4QPt5q0AsWDmPoPSoVEP01SfmJk9lsF3a2xmUdhPtLzVfbs1jSZcaN2jJZ/lJJasCRnXmUIGVi+sJt58jVSJhZ7bRnmUVMnNlP5rV1L6gQ3JxWyMktr5SiC3PKaDZ8Ir3iSwoHXkzdmC0A00DPErXzUrWTh/2U5iQHnTMtCIdgzvCeqE4CamBiYxeB+H9ClU6c9HZkcdOgoHNY0AxgBI1bSrUevi5AH4beBuKXViL8+HQm51VfFZrsUKzfGVugTUofdz0Ir7iMbtxEaOTqO718ucFgRVhERidvJWqfiz5L92nvhwhlqiMMUEu3FcTKdx/OZO5mbsk5Y/ksCL1/12SUa0LPhUEh5enL94hVlG9FQUfd27Kq2MPq+05M88TJrBYR5NU/lY+9eWD3zcvp4WsFdwa1qD2LOtC0AZ9MAKLs0W1tPTqvZ8ZXAWIVudiaT1VLNKXouHLUrN3cNMQKSGqh3U008vOR8L55QAWGEN7fi+8NMQb8ppjHi1/7FGXhbYqZqsNs9rUR2Fxmg7rY3omw\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15030","langCode":"vi","question":"LVLmWAcwaVlVJ/IXnEw5J7gFEsLGcO/4HVAeXjSojpFqS08Wuph42EwdW0ClHSliuGAggpSQvMidWEbPpd76XkQBSZZd7N3YZ2/K/pi04la1VQ4N2KPa6Oq54EplOl8Z","answers":["had","is","was","has"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE/VgWzMkVUpENZ5gb8diYcyQ7zuyQ1iy6U30YX4tawf76pC0CPFSATBNDJNYejScvKeVQk/KZfk554tZXYNNehlNT6gItndVIVaXVDm7HG478Bh3FRbrrnp079hem96pQC0oI8hyJSjEjAHh7eP/1EynU2bFAnv/zKcAxQNstlS3WHvub9XU/vHSIwklkeCXIACBxPdZ4hyNKpofNg721EuxA4dTK3BEqmzkMvsH064Sd7nZ0X9Z7vjQgYLBCTrhB4f4b+Ngcsc1ki2x0YuRK+kf2sHGk0HlrIoSgqqiZXvFn8Auuxk94ee747yOHVxy3TH30UBzx/orJ6A3gqkQmk/FNp9axvWs+BoaLOF3tWvSk915IODH4vSxIsDghpZJwGM/BcKeDv2upuMyCrTOv2n6O0u1ZGd9hMuUt48fwJJfdVQzEqhCZG8s7GEKvTvdKFrtagkcc41RfSfRO9nol0jNGF0rgfkfUSHCykOQDbEZ9bEW0U8Ozxm2ctAqsJMC3JZK9PJw5C+gh8fDkhSlKAfdRMRmuofTWzMHqb6qsn7fyxKmV/1x4WpOriWbJ+76tQ\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15031","langCode":"vi","question":"CSnTFE/uIhmYzskUXsXeU6MaVioTKf6SnTSdq+rYDdE3XqFOqQp6q9lytdNzR+nfnVMVqv3VRSYcaYurIkrgFFwiRD1M5gR2tFJLui4R5Nkez1tiA1DOySLaUQ6pszPg","answers":["is","does","are","do"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE49be4R4WzVa5fsdIVHX0GEvFUfg12o+AEBSL6R5L1XwPJBfnrU3D2Kfi7zgNemMluGyME5yI6FaEFmmNmApyyVSjydrobamYVlLUt8eZf8AFJ7qHoQqIdFpJOe2PGP3TEDndeRcpAdle1DiXrb2HGUFtqBj4IgLdC/Cf/S6TGc23IIntfiESy/8K9rpKgNECVW9SmAzhja0pj2xCDDQ3j7OSrg5GLRHILx2xvsxJgsROuTrPcCApa8PiRzyFp2cOr2rUdBnGRPTd1qJquzcU22oH5ssfx7rcNN2MsiKVDUTbasp7fmPm17clSBO/q1q/xQEqQ+MB6LHzmT/rJiQatuzcV3JU28A+ua3RfQ04nzIMH9mlWj+GkaHMvwClIPIyF0HQQwIzEq+iW5pGKQbXWEr3Rrv6NrVXWxzTq59d4u//VRaMH6KGLVtAkl1uSaw/QCBxPdZ4hyNKpofNg721EuxA4dTK3BEqmzkMvsH064StYFgzb5tqbgMgkm1caQaASmPArTbzWEIMrftz5sN+IojopHeaiq0vwPvC79TJSTpagwHjovcCTneMU9rd70XEWdGPlq75nKwMN5/GK1/rlLUUqkH3bCSAHPr1X2hj9MHL/4yUJ3QxEO5aYdBxtgBZEUuMsn0wDvZqIsXBTwrf6kmPrLtFcccORTAmQBN+Hf00h7M4tJ4mpmZPzj+OqcYP6wjnCWTTHkAYAGey/7ODe4\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15032","langCode":"vi","question":"uhzD7SDpm2kUb6eor4O2v50EYO5uCmgEgbwnVVHgDeFdeP234Bj8nlbKDgb2H7j2YHdlvcL6MbDgHD9CJ2JbY2SiUcPjeoJ9cI6fBKpjQiurD+UUUcpKPCdplk9n7lalri1+BGPvJvVYlD/IwMe2Nw\u003d\u003d","answers":["is","was","were","are"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE5vG30cd2iEGrXKsgkPyARyQ7zuyQ1iy6U30YX4tawf7LgOAdHa5d4rZWpuN87by56cIu37HeMsSWwwEG9EsJGNr4rMnhgUHNK7mOWgUOrLFaSKIvFapHrSZ9BxOGboSRGMbDcE/UaYgGXLC05IhTTuEmMcKh7nBVTxVctrbX+myQAGmRimktpLYGluPbn944T1ssbtIyYD/laMnliRrtfUZXy0nSkYULl2TLhkJU4HL7KNO3gXboDMgWMSwWEA1Atg2Om8lGxdiuacuzySSF2+0G+lVov+NNUkaLdFPJJ1JNcKb85FwSA+1H5nX7JwY1okdETEDqRB/KNqhIxCd/8OamJzGQsGl/k4cLeaArNKDVB8hu50ztjKjlC/XxarqDu/hTvaqa2+ESb6xDS4JK0ThgpFKs4VrblutyVrR5CWI/E5niG2eo2dD7CV00lphbhHAiAN9aE8t2LhArs0q5DhrkQL10KzNZiA4/JDdu2ZZDLuCO/c/Z31GCE+IFrIzNz1ssbtIyYD/laMnliRrtfUZXy0nSkYULl2TLhkJU4HLHn+pYujjmgav7UmNMn4J2kHGTc4C6i8wE2l6lkk4ogVd7rVdaw4YcnvY1n4MxO9r9+TjhPOgBcXWmk8gTqLR2ao3JYF51a/MDdeuJSXRB6QMdQ+JNcC2XsVrbt+v/A5n6qQQGZKVPRzXQaPZ7i1vkXZrAp8jXYAdmqv8T+VHGn2l+DHH/2/mRxsISMyvFNjjCJLyoucm7E9tRKuNi3LCDN4HmKx3EN1IdAU2oOPi6hs\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15033","langCode":"vi","question":"RW9/kXWN3BU81V8IG7O+HLd9VMAcdN0DaNu9x7mYiayxnNlO+MkwbbCwvKU7rnalrzOqq/Lh51jKk5xQs6TCEMFzES2mIKuQDWragE5m6rDNSmgNIwEMdoCssF/IaDSSGhk2XLj8B+ChS//UG5dj5A\u003d\u003d","answers":["does","do","didn’t","did"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE8JsLnrYmID1kPAyyvxwAKWQ7zuyQ1iy6U30YX4tawf7mQpTA9bNW3+TqpXqbkQ7nA62s/5p1afzBlvgHaXxcJl+cAY0i4SqbVWa5Bmoz6PiwCLQSPKmtI8tutYKMLfCRPSbgb22DtSMR6kVuQ7ts/rA7dU9iMVZygGa6fcp7OND0EX2P1Gv+ijWbpWEwW9vaGy91RwK2vC/wmfWHKZQ9Cve70CkGfYUdlwRDvGMZovQJSb0IDgBqJLCTvjFe7ps15Itgv5dHhR0jeqUrsrJnsiFRXwLUWDBOxyDr0I/VFL9Hfa2Ih+IRTyy+hUKN5rPp0Ej5ZrNJr+pMN6InMA2XixCgvMBk75EGJx9YaLksr4gP9JFZ9sfnnqe4kXrHxG20gW9aUCJM23ummSEmBdrzabOg1nz7ckqLxvDtXVHKVs0auuqs3/apRFCPEw525KDN5EdMlGSi0xRXsZ84imt7+bAItBI8qa0jy261gowt8JEsud3aOosiAJD7bT9V55J+l258BvBgwU/A2qNoDhGcHsknilGFyTKQIMXCTePbRyChfFOd1RneiH357ocjAe9PEOKnkecerVD6sNjb6YIDAdaLw1ir4D4WVjcXMBux+Aik2wimEEQk2uGE4Jo18AAiGa585mnIzo51QVYAX26lZxYdr0n4o22sDxXpNFAf8DwMzGuCmSFpaJ/gB4BMch4Xc3kt+2ZjnC6Jgtj78P7nug\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15034","langCode":"vi","question":"gZ9ymRFwawYouekVi3cRhd/Y+vUSScQYN5foqUnvBiy5AajtpTIwNh6/012fdUdWQ4HfPWEF+FeYEuRcmlSdpQmA2rYbk7Ue/MxU9fNznVF4CZavU/iDE9xNrfxH+HV/Ju+qRDy4cFR5cUzeS/0vAw\u003d\u003d","answers":["shouldn’t","won’t","should","will"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEzXomgASnMzjDcQ9sQLkShvPoi+o5W7wGb8Ssd4dYx6wDxzDhWXJtLUguQDGghIEeTKaFAipu5+CaZZ7b7dKh8A7LSQwy1TTBA1DdOaSaD9BUZ4ypDF+2eB/8WN7lXewiqHLwmIYpuhO8u9VjFzF7zecrteLGMFOkExang2laCqmWhEDINjkWDrztlNUD9gBOZa/erpx9I794P2aCjWX9t6O1/QaWjPHczOQELCZuA4qe0OJmLLlPSrRgGnvk/fPL/ZDcD2PSZjCF5JNFfh5EplELXH+ApEahelKdMF4PQosDlLJUq8ZLuX1MR2G3GFs2FDkFH/K+zlJXsH8azdozq3HnJPOKTezhA+RVZasQBJqVt+zZCC/ltJwZeUT9Yp1XWuKa0tVkewjrnpvvcgyNe2vwQOwUw7uleWP6fSm9IqR+39ztdGNh/pTyd0rqfT1Bk7fRBFWuAaKYkicg/yTQVgLeZMEL5KrPm3yONiFA733OiCAwT4lLMLrL57FBwbdX5ctPyfJOQj5aXNE4JKKf8oGUGVOSyeqqe9BvlLemG35qVarDU73s3VtC9CFIZsd0iQDauVA2ti2neJuDl7IqRPIFih1SK0Wvw6pXncZtMcNEzt0jIlGUXALZKVydhaMLkRROX1C9qkmaoftAriLBLPg1xLnBMQJ/aahgru97gESHoUvzRC7B5oweSEO1+sMqjZXtbE1z3+NgC1fLlHxg9ek48CICBZcItvDOicM+W41"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15035","langCode":"vi","question":"PSx4Yit0w4/jzbCEW5n+Q7uB3ImOKeIK3KvXWASRZNCWV4tF8HG3OEtFccdSjmkwdr57q6QBCGZb56oX7LU4wg\u003d\u003d","answers":["doesn’t","don’t","do","didn’t"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE6XwK1B2o6qAiMA3M1ev/SUsqtY7LgNeGTJt2aJQ+mbn6GvPVWyYTQ9MpVfFoS6uQKYB11ep7jSoAKWb3fu704Za2NZo7Y/3hDD+8SjoAA9WF//V1I/zn+twSEhm3QKwP3x6htKtlLUszhBC5NP889Fsu6d3sdjCMJUIC95rQxUWb1tBD5NauJSXqo+D1081sc0zCJSmgw16C0rx8BroRBTBfqoVdiKCX4WGcBMVH7Xx76gl/HYoT2I0pFMo7TuNdDPhvwcTK2PW9rWfeQH90sasNay2WGKt6DQV6H9bPk6owbAao1106z8CW9X5GbgU7Ng2Om8lGxdiuacuzySSF29fTmywRxHuTr2NkgjTl6PmsSG8rnJ9+cIKDOgIzUTmC2xJWXLjelC56rcgxkjoB8vrcJvZnY0HCUotctmR7lMpvESi+DmTBpQtqllIBUa3V3I5BqWWF4NFaPU3Y4qAUR9pHwiekhj3pb9b5hS3cRl1tVUODdij2ujqueBKZTpfGQ\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15036","langCode":"vi","question":"40UnjTB+MPwFUAHUTxKR7TBNufZGu2NvSKNM8+6pqkLPH0Tm3bPUveR2YG8tdG6oOCblGuv4VHaqy4gxIsJVzQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["what","when","who","why"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE6/Qf9uYdGtWh5qcWGpsHTydyHFm8I5NgxtN+ZYVsiF5HMfY0J9NMg2vvRpcA5SvKlYjWVlk4OxmQY/9Q0L8s6eqe1DsAY3OdOb5JOZQ52ewUOQUf8r7OUlewfxrN2jOrceck84pN7OED5FVlqxAEmqkfTW7bb9jcNFkSkL3ywkAnc58CnpHEpwyIiUmNHGw46JFLsBdF1fQnoGpC4R/IqSaqRdpnaEA+nHi6MHswACACXx2nlIxGIRD9vlt2ubDU1LNKXouHLUrN3cNMQKSGqigSp4mI1I/JbOO0n7jXhpp7FVUIcdribc+rZVDCBBFHAmpP6cfHJoK7V01CVoQD7TB9g/DNe9m1t8YKnypCJN/t2QEnE88C6irzk6giHVjIvR6BjHSX3U3Ar6PYB3X3mgeabA7xxQterRoq6akf1KRaiMOq6tWa0W2LN1zq6VjzBKxyJB0nnBCkCHucS5o7ySu5AphUpdfpSQRQ52MWcQl0OVlHG5vgEeiwzagFQBwIg\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15037","langCode":"vi","question":"r5+Qxw8Uw/QMoBgHHA1csezi6N1lnvC0hWk6f2dR8wHKvRAsSHyIkcYJi63ONdgc","answers":["when","why","what","which"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE4QPt5q0AsWDmPoPSoVEP01YoWcwYul81ShTeRSFfmwoVfbs1jSZcaN2jJZ/lJJasCRnXmUIGVi+sJt58jVSJhZ7bRnmUVMnNlP5rV1L6gQ3JxWyMktr5SiC3PKaDZ8Ir3iSwoHXkzdmC0A00DPErXzUrWTh/2U5iQHnTMtCIdgzljhiwlb0DZfbyFAE25P3t0T4XWzfaJVkmHXO8lwVg2TDpW/nYLwhOaULPXJtW9qWVY9O+0twqIwiONc5dBG1l07WIuICukcHpBFO75kyEfgQqFSODFhoJfjcBUff7b0BGWX6KMAl76O6K0gD69RzjVixmVamNuxFrXDhA7paIlIqRP0AG6o04eahJHS/6HwJQCmGDFiQ2n5mfCjSk4j6VySNm6c4VxvMvactlhYX7t8xFDN5yqwukx7hg/Zxe+ye5LubTjkfXF2RC5z0/BxG/3WfsdpSzooMWQin35JxH9HttuR4xye2yV0UDZMC/7YT6wZqj5/XzpW5eRcMQ1YhWmDSb7I6c5VhQKA9Tnii07wWKHxkyyhiUGJcWMtUrkeeSueAisQqmRuCMRCjILzO+TTzowfYuHxQ8qV1NldT+lXvr2xu0I8/pStXCzvYiB3h"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15038","langCode":"vi","question":"2Bh9tRWsHvMjEs8hg+t2tAWVqVIxT14vSWVVT6ZwWCTykGzKMyAnNdx4dsS8hjzwCIEnoKJuzxFOI81KmQOENnzCF8naWSFCLTt/wt43VbKbzEeQPwip6WQstf1YWHL7","answers":["couldn’t","should","could","shouldn’t"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE0Vdb3H8PXF0a75dbS0J3h/fhtozJXOPxBC+YvJcyBKX5WhVyv6rvCRbx9zfKHlVnj29edg8L+sTTAcP4iH4cjDUK0B4nc7yCMI2NO3H4pBnse6fA8629TMXsxDgm1kWBhlGNbl0h8oEQsGKO0f+oLc10lc7T7q7iNXXR52bYlBSElRAVavRdFeDWQ3mKGb3T2Ch2e0EfSsNsy4G2waiAWPt7KDlANuWJ8d+wzPEN+pV/LbU6merETsQuzHcrR5Dr5ijTEpGbMoeq8vgTdwqupqA1kWjOw6rmOn/gIBqLBiSyrHtiQupctEilYG+huavAdljwXQU+WYMY595jQo4oWpDu5HVqaln6HDF+JxTNxiWm+dT6zSm8hBTJhRkeSa4kL67P1beNMPQIIXLnxL2Xo9PQIfKnnB3noHtOg61xLDga82fUl3ogNN8SUITzSkZfyHMI1w/8Lm6TaBee4XwigZzk0+I5G0gASo6rQwgbmB3+/OopvXjsJ0s6D80ZV1pODpX9UkJbEqCuCI77UWRTBLB9m7nhqu+SKWQaPnO/u2kTEeQmWz6Z5XFrTAv/IBNA/jc9pOAdkyzYX57XFaNCpxyheuBdDipzrv4TQYONubW"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15039","langCode":"vi","question":"24QCfsLvGGqpIJFOvrCTupBlv3hdLn930E+W9rHc7D61Ry8LaSrQgExF8OHwdtZvdOw/HBJ4/j3aZoUDMbozppwHtumcI4Qw2tsMeTk73k8\u003d","answers":["are","was","aren’t","were"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE5+w2E6SJeQEYFPIEmFlJrBf/AGAMQzac9W4Dx16GwgMAR6DDz96S+qX1i1IyW/Pt7+2Nk7Q9TyFIU/Yb7vCQOQ4uXvOL8mMCl1BHsLfqmoyo94/m3jxd9zPm3WenKLqk0bVaX4gXX9kQrQLc6o+rP2yzZ2j/I1WBguPHwtNth3IaSfmTKhakN2po9+UDoni7deO02feC7fVG0ICHrjRnrdieJVpOUneFFDGRSYw2EWNU2bHqJ27C3Q/wJzP4cpF9zPNSOzRiT/oybxGhUNZUYgDDaRbmevtNUN2ZYhrVzngI4VBuOvFnFxaMoF8koGU0/G0W6AmaUNZDxEwWhp0A+lo41vQe83/Y7LaLBVM5s8lRfY3fl/qQ9K+NGJf3Rep1ysiYxxfqmfROkKG2u/USY8r1F2ICPmT0WcLQ1F6Ok8dLigMxayf6o5y62NnpuprGzrk6z3AgKWvD4kc8hadnDq9q1HQZxkT03daiars3FNtY/KnhS2av5a9wUKndYBjJwGdY5gsKiO9ce38o9NYSUq5pS1apEL8F582Tinjs04rKXs1NPW0werMEkH3dwhEa7yaFo2sy06hDfjIPwdDZsC6T+RsdHHP74UrVTX0/pPVb1dfrMPNgKhey1c25bMBUpPuM4RWeOLYvg2M4b+7K/I\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15040","langCode":"vi","question":"KdJsLGm3h1TppgWNNLat/f5Evim0q/pnFA7nMJK6r4nw75ytUDhxlXNygyYSVz9zaQrxKkQ7Sw5bN5phJpGWxQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["do","did","does","don’t"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE8JsLnrYmID1kPAyyvxwAKX8WeK08x5hkjUCM+YhS+MhVxtoCKTVVd1HoK7xHBethH6uL6ehSA3MEI7nOba9XTDN1NPbI3EmxXKWzG7n5yLfBVdfBcw1E2BkeV/Cpb9KbaLQixOFEasS//NEzBA1ETxq66qzf9qlEUI8TDnbkoM37kaGQpyvJciAk7yJsc8CGMAi0EjyprSPLbrWCjC3wkReYWIBvXeDCQf5GLqOxx/k45wDr4aPlaZwDEs+vyF0/KPTsUaWbeexuPVYj7wiw3JiiM+4ZVQF168PY5rWH6xlplQyOa9V8Xe34GI9apVrudCP7InHhHp0zotDyJo1t28HcDPaRfkp638zNZ2q1pnizMlGFREbzYaiDVVqrhFqsQ\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15041","langCode":"vi","question":"6lUA2BZbwr79549Pc8Rvs86QMGE40Vlvp1mqsV40g/25p4CVuf5G/Hrb0k0fOC0N+CJJadqqH56WSS+ygboWaXd6anOfh8y+yzxAYWn43nE\u003d","answers":["when","how","which","why"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE/QH+Pdy7OgSVBbX8nh4IEE9yV6x5nljsb7preunuC+v0SPxf3FBa03DLIaQ4ugWIe0IXLxY6SmiPePuSepVcYU1RofVsk/QpQ0G3o0zsn5AwCJENSH5PzaDmvPNunH+sGNqwGoz6zsTdkHFrNP7uBm2H8EOs15dhNvoJpdmsoB2qea7WQaOwDWtGWrOs0zexJU0VM0lW4pNZlLUS/n1J7fq9V3NwmAt6APFS4iVPBD+WU8TkVAABz10dhz/YdC7iUJxaseTomDiZoKxTK40TMsp+ES2vb82tReJ8ZLWYu14dRWRjit922zzvpg8rS4E6HPrMdecEsl4aJY/MozD5N3PlP5F4k1g9QaBYN1SbvVqY+8B6R5+S6zgxj+pQCprL/hvlvObxDVnNwG0KwoFnBSSAOsw709fuNGFHY+9E3yxdyDvidNU5yEDGm5toXM6PqWzbqrLEnMO++fBczir8/YQUjy/K+f7I16hs/lVVLa3SKrtH5ewsgXmTFxGIieVK70QppCAVkSuj7Kl1yUc3utbi0+1wmImTzdDdNTFi5uWK+iftp8X0cTb13EpRqwMoJTuid8cxtWQW+J4BEANNaIhWma8URkbJ2y04txL210HNKL3O8E2ZvAupveZzVAZDA\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15042","langCode":"vi","question":"oE8ywS84AjgjdEEbrQAHBTxCbvVoAy1pob2+RaZp5+ZxIGdOWRl7HQo20AIs57OE0majr6X5hymgEEiy2ny7I8EPYFWwUytPUZ2VWtCTPVXamEFhq0A5S8PVu2CMjEBn","answers":["is","were","was","are"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE/TT1DYlNaTG4EUA/J8uO2K8MYQOXZ2FQASHLDHmEFfemoMqbEhdAnJIwN9FtHDurp3eFyoLKdLwW88j5yHKrjiRWVxXiNQ/T6S/iOb9f0wj0Dzu2DKHCMTtaDAYhTU1azd0p7TeIjO/y2Pwnt63PzEWHgTO2+4T2xH4gy12AMwvsXQlr2xDs63sjCe5ohmPORR37sir8jz1davkQ0m4t0teqc/oBgdi/83vZLnrt8hQT0CHyp5wd56B7ToOtcSw4GvNn1Jd6IDTfElCE80pGX8pPukwnXIPBRdjxc7ro+JLJ3Bzg4jEEp5H47iUip8bSrDqjuRZRRHCBpoPUQNyB7YTvkVD4rgxj5CJD3kRPah5KRHadcQchjBXXzfAyUrsRvvsdayAUXX0hvHmA4S+OvLMpAT5F3i//mTDhJLWeiA2pGvv9tMzU/OdfeUFvMbO0g\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15043","langCode":"vi","question":"gAK9B0LHsF4mG4C8WR7qmMtZIfaCVUyYjhR2MzBZLJgHbtDumAP5b1fp5fYJ+c2N3HnbzRKRKHvoGVgWT4yk4G6QiWBf8jtL1OF5BlqcTLYZmvULq13QMzlVAET7xaPW","answers":["when","why","which","where"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE+SxEbEg5DchXqXFOXrU4soFe3GX/Q6Bypo7X/PcPeVohHk1T+Vj715YPfNy+nhawes6U/ARWQ9Vhc+7TC9jpOLXpAONmj+bqrrkFr+SwSQNFFSa5m004+9dY3cl/MWGw9g2Om8lGxdiuacuzySSF2+0G+lVov+NNUkaLdFPJJ1Jz3QIpthEo+JTkJf8rqcvk4P9R1rk3soUMOTxKlYq+NKVnLDxBJlL7u7MkOlZJGerRZpWrk6JX/wDalT7nJzAYtwJqEeA2HI/6kOdG0Ji0N49kIK/toAmPwtL2k3saFXq84txs4jlxIwMoPYt0yxbW99xRcWCCg+xiCRRL2VamP9CobO+RNZ5rhV0ZrM7N4QKvRCmkIBWRK6PsqXXJRze64RPNsISEhbY+0MPTaKWnVCu8tU7r75NG/5deJHR9enmp4YIqgh3ItgPDe8Hcf2pOvn7Bj9qEApILS4mmWUdWH0blyowNqSGscoCxch3/m5xMyLshsexs6XV1IdzxsUNL0R64N4AdFmf3B5YP7AM+NEuWhE7ILFD0EdeDfaXJiQV"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15044","langCode":"vi","question":"NfVv3pIDIGsAM/sWt2dpabrKvMshHgGLmkEundrT95vx22blOYHH3FVI/m8uRDzlYKg4dbLDlMR/9wgLoiGd8w\u003d\u003d","answers":["should","do","can","must"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE5TJt6VbRhecao0W7/xxXI49PIGv45Xs836RL3H1X2uKv6WmEadjJ/LOHvsFulo6cHkX+rKIKl4Dl4EDQJ2E2IfMc7t2nMFCBrC7er0UZ/bONoLrF9g40jvDC9GgkXXDPbWhb9NV4vLcTBvn3iqXv0MlJvQgOAGoksJO+MV7umzXWndh44Z3aIsgDRteHqcox1lsw+Y/0RcrMkeSrd/eAm4R4G/6gXM25IgyST109UjBNj6ojjah448z+yPBSO7udvOMDtOUQaIOB7h0Jl/yGxS4KXgABzCpTwsrF1SFN+yfqSDQYrqgC86dJ0ZD2lTyo0EFHWj3fBujIh8cab1FmeoT9OWT19diDXGcSYiZzQZ+"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15045","langCode":"vi","question":"JmhdTEcdcsTLAiLFI2O9aLaBDgnvI0keN0454NWLu9+Nah7Zy5VA2tGhjn5BoDshXo0kHDu8WhK86J0mCHvyeFOQkBFxYGMRXW2TDfXQ1261VQ4N2KPa6Oq54EplOl8Z","answers":["couldn’t","shouldn’t","could","should"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE72AMa24Abq6RqxBXNpH3y/0y9FD+dZwtEwqKwMDoR8v6HpOVkiE50kTlVh5/ae6EPC6LyCEc25sw3z5Xx2Lwf2JM6ZeDHJz5rhp1fwXno9Wr06wVH/t2FaYAXno2t39QGAPDHJedMaEgVzYM6fK3NyxtEDdOZ9SSqhBjb3AI0jY2DY6byUbF2K5py7PJJIXb7Qb6VWi/401SRot0U8knUko1YPrDSjf/cBia/lhLmxqSqDa3jpGeKJ7zC5Td7Q5gc6VN7z8cTLVlx6CNrJIhlt8MsItowAYkWg97J88JM25VQICaiXq0NJlyqgfGAEH8T7rzKEjN5X6IYbfXi1w3RDyp1WiNoWAPXFJgzktGpYvhG8yGSMvH/7wUDZiLf6R4Q\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15046","langCode":"vi","question":"3p1g2Rdxwumj5fmUk/DICw14zQELcQSR4nnkSljXG1kUF7KSvTEb1jJqoCT6qtbsVvlGJWITLHXuqygTOfxymJ26EyLrGrCJWXxUcSGeqhk\u003d","answers":["should","shouldn’t","wouldn’t","would"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEwRNovpFzO6839xaae3MJ4AdYzxogFawNuX9ANtYBqIs7x9JJZvsOEZJKh7a1dqcw/gxa2KvbgnnX9DRV31uQS3HmhjsonQnCuZ59rt1Sjx0+B9wxSoy5JlG3z80OyhRDNdmlsE9hQpnJ1XIpoBF9xhFJ8UsE1DvDNE5l0y6ejhk7oPVX0Gw0pUXhutpdpTOffgmXcdukA+o9XJ3JpxXs5hS8alGZdAqIU8LpwjX9a0ToPvbv7svKlWsYtMhL+evTRtAdvXU8HC8rpnbVCiG+b94lgBq+7vkyPzgox/ZEcPcolkNIX8/fTkhNUx4gvyQWQZJBz0cfJ27PK17bWlZEtw\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15047","langCode":"vi","question":"vXYLmplAoSjlOuPEZhlCyIpQo7TbfYbRJCTLzar4Ibwd8mu3imdEDAthN/tIp1VuhG8yGSMvH/7wUDZiLf6R4Q\u003d\u003d","answers":["shouldn’t","should","would","wouldn’t"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEwRNovpFzO6839xaae3MJ4AHOuEz4MnA6fTm9QGlYjS3Gq57z1GD9P0ETBAxprsDNSJecmoUpxAIwduWLXfqNumls26qyxJzDvvnwXM4q/P24YCeUtdNSY5li+wNCcV62MK3Db1hBgtr7rRzlfxLfa8WuZMD5HrTazC5Cl7sF8kqqCsWcK+Zi7DYqhzVaQ9iDSvgK60sHkWrBdtsYLz6Y4c04F1YlzQwyQAc1DS0r5wX45wDr4aPlaZwDEs+vyF0/KPTsUaWbeexuPVYj7wiw3JSedyoTZSiLrWuYcNH/XPaUICXGKvP0o/ukgnMZiZCPrICmqyP5qmBbtmY54eDbZtZDwQjSVQCGa2ZQ0Gz3pwPaFQeyotwi4dzSH27yj3tWw\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15048","langCode":"vi","question":"AOnaVT0nWGjIUSS/E7dcfAHd0V/+zePKIJKcshdiWf+2JnsfZPtDlE+BRYBElVW9","answers":["can","must","should","shall"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE74j9SpT+8guoPxpp3oz8Jgm1hwPttHy6DUTfXFNgSSjv3aJXXh4GHcQegD99gkbLlmiu4n7igUIJoECU8bqAtqqVlF118PDFtu7zJNQCxpKpuYv5XuAFYY9SkSfV/D3o/JEeMhIgC6PiqSs8rJCj8dFJ8UsE1DvDNE5l0y6ejhk7oPVX0Gw0pUXhutpdpTOfVKj8KsPNKhWmdhFFHAkweXoek9e9LQ4PbWq8p45qn7+snH7h851FRod8cVpsqmrsdN1GoC991DujYPmrDf42LWT7jOEVnji2L4NjOG/uyvy"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15049","langCode":"vi","question":"JmhdTEcdcsTLAiLFI2O9aE51pZ1GgrKLs3jmsioryCt1MEkCFqOy5U058tjsr+TlCfp05rECcIronYPbL7Rg22QkhVLAPkL/H5p5LyxlxTIrchrAMs8NRgQSrgliUeachYTjK+CS3KpIawTCdSwz9uZKJ+pzQVxOkoh/l23vNqPb3VgBV2BxyN5FCqtoKynrPmCEDKIuvBI+9HNk27AMUQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["should","could","will","must"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEwyoXJBK9b48YsIcBBbjb6KHgOBiUraygN+foTvsa30dMLjKCiPiazsfRbGtYjNMMr+lphGnYyfyzh77BbpaOnA3uJF4OcztiSoZKt1dMiqpypXSkaX58omvM3oBqC0/1lzb//61we73UGNSC6Bcij1Khkph8T3bZYKPngrYVgFCuD3HWmWEXGbNn1tAjC4MAac9HZkcdOgoHNY0AxgBI1brJ2SwPrIgoGm3qItI8iNWv2GLIwTz6RWU34latxMupuvHqufiQ77GNUwFxiNBGbIFCvNf5qkWjMbredpsaW/qLh1zjDF3L68B/QJW1CcaiR5Ahu/P2MbFsxZXIuimyMEqEObe1JMyzPAC7nJYyoq+Izhnq9ZFyB9LUqkd290t07v2c1disM7gck8PcsEB/xpqqo740ZR8SVx1LcReYP+yuTX2mcco4/tE7/fV5U2GjDpoIodtl2U8tTpwqxFXQIqfrDK+1Kb1ZHWiQZHMWmsFtVUODdij2ujqueBKZTpfGQ\u003d\u003d"}]